
Garuda Indonesia!
﻿

How do you get to the viewing mall..Is it for﻿ passengers only or anyone can go?

no valuair.﻿

Valuair has join forces with jetstar.﻿

thanks for that. are there any viewing﻿ malls in the other terminals??

Yes. Terminal 2 and﻿ 3 have viewing malls too.

hi, great video. is this the best place﻿ to view the aircraft at changi?? it looks a great position. how much of the traffic can be seen from here..thanks

Well only﻿ traffic on NorthCross and Terminal 1 can be seen from here!

nice﻿ video :)
Thumbs up!

Thanks man ! Glad you like it :D:D﻿

i bet you﻿ liked the CX taking off there

Hahahahaha :P﻿

I thought Etihad uses 777﻿ to SIN?
Anyways, I REALLY LOVE IT! :)):D

Nope. They use A332﻿ :D

aww. so﻿ QR and Emirates are the only ME carrier using 777 in SIN? :D

That's right !﻿

haha. :)) well in my place there are actually around 8 airlines operating 777s in and﻿ out of there :)):D and some are on double daily service :D

Wow.. i didnt know TK sends their﻿ A340 to SIN, and nice catch of the Etihad Airways as well as Air France! and of course the cool livery Jetstar... what a fruitful day haha

Actually they were taken﻿ on two different days :D
